<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dan Wright</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dan Wright</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 21:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First Quarter Consumption Opportunities</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/q4recs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/q4recs/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to make a quick note of some of the best content I have consumed in 2023 so far &amp;ndash; especially the new releases. If you trust my judgement, check them out!
FilmPuss in Boots: The Last Wish is my favourite release of the year so far. All of the elements come together brilliantly: vivid animation, fantastic characters, genuinely funny moments, and a surprisingly mature story that makes it feel like the Logan of the Shrek franchise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student Voice</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/clarevoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/clarevoice/</guid>
      <description>After I graduated in 2020, I was asked to provide an article for the Clare Review. I recently found a copy online while looking for something else. For posterity, I reproduce the following from said online version, which also features the excellent Jonty Townson and some nostalgic photos.Dan Wright (2017)UCS President
As the outgoing UCS president and a recent graduate, my final year at Clare was one of my best; for obvious reasons, it was also one of the worst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>219,948</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/covid/</guid>
      <description>I want to pay tribute to the National COVID Memorial Wall. Today was its second anniversary, and I visited by chance during a break from the office.
Despite walking that stretch of the Thames quite often, the wall never fails to move me. It&amp;rsquo;s a supremely poignant monument to the devastation that COVID-19 caused, or was allowed to cause, in the UK. The simple act of walking the path provides the time to reflect on those days and the lives we lost (literally and figuratively).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Write</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/why-i-write/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/why-i-write/</guid>
      <description>George Orwell is one of my favourite authors. His famous essay, which the title of this post references, is well worth a read.
To state the obvious: this is no great essay, and I am no Orwell. But I wanted to set out some of my reasons for having a blog. If you&amp;rsquo;re familiar with the motives for writing that he presents, you will recognise them in varying proportions in the below:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://example.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>Please feel free to contact me via email.
If you know me personally, please don&amp;rsquo;t use that email.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
