<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dan Wright</title>
    <link>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dan Wright</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://danwright.org.uk/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes from 2023</title>
      <link>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/2023/</guid>
      <description>Some quick reflections on my 2023. All are personal, but the first three err on the side of the professional.
I significantly improved my well-being this year compared to last by building more positive interactions into my basic lifestyle (e.g. walking to work, living with friendly flatmates, working in a social office). This is blindingly obvious, but you do need to seek those opportunities out as they aren&amp;rsquo;t a given. In the Civil Service, I usually worked from home three days out of five because my colleagues would go in two days a week &amp;ndash; and 90% of a day in the office could be spent apart from colleagues due to hot-desking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Write</title>
      <link>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/whyiwrite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/whyiwrite/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to set out my rationale for having a blog. George Orwell once gave four motives for writing, present in every writer in varying proportions:
Sheer egoism. Aesthetic enthusiasm. Historical impulse. Political purpose. My current motivations are a mix of 1, 2, and 4. In my own words, I would codify them as:
By the time I shuffle off this mortal coil, I would like to have some words on the record, regardless of the number of people who substantially care or remember them &amp;ndash; though I obviously hope it will more than zero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Consumer Surplus</title>
      <link>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/shoppinglist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/shoppinglist/</guid>
      <description>Inspired by Consumer Surplus, I thought it would be fun to suggest some economical things that I think add significant value to my life.
I know this is quite weird, but at the same time, I find it interesting to learn from other people&amp;rsquo;s experiences so I figured I might as well share my own. Personal finance is one case where I&amp;rsquo;ve definitely benefited from the research done by others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading List</title>
      <link>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/readinglist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 20:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/readinglist/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s some books or articles I&amp;rsquo;d recommend. I can&amp;rsquo;t claim this list is some sort of cohesive narrative, but I&amp;rsquo;d say all of these have something of merit regardless of political persuasion. I will add to this.
Keep in mind that because I would like to have a job, this is not an exhaustive list of everything I consider worthwhile reading.
Politics The Art of War, Sun Tzu.
The History of the Peloponnesian War, Thucydides.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
