<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dan Wright</title>
    <link>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dan Wright</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://danwright.org.uk/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fast Stream</title>
      <link>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/civilservice1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/civilservice1/</guid>
      <description>To save myself grief, and for the avoidance of doubt, everything in this post relates to my experiences and opinions only. These are my views &amp;ndash; certainly not those of past or present employers, nor past or present colleagues.I spent three years in the Civil Service. This was an eye-opening experience of government which I really did enjoy.
It was precisely because I spent those years in the Civil Service that I was unsurprised to see the news of a collapse in Civil Service Fast Stream applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why</title>
      <link>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/whyiwrite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/whyiwrite/</guid>
      <description>Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a Substack Andy or posting to Instagram, I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s weird to maintain a slightly self-indulgent online presence. The only thing I&amp;rsquo;ve done differently is set up a GitHub pages blog instead of a newsletter.
With that lamp-shading in place:
George Orwell once gave four motives for writing, present in every writer in varying proportions:
Sheer egoism. Aesthetic enthusiasm. Historical impulse. Political purpose. About each of these, I&amp;rsquo;d say:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading List</title>
      <link>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/readinglist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 20:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/readinglist/</guid>
      <description>Keep in mind that because I would like to have a job, this is not an exhaustive list of everything I consider worthwhile reading.
Utopia and Dystopia One of my favourite courses at university was the Politics of the Future course taught by Prof Duncan Bell. I found a later version of the course guide which has many great recommendations and puts them in context.
I appreciate these may just as well belong under the sci-fi section.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
