<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dan Wright</title>
    <link>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dan Wright</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://danwright.org.uk/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What I saw at Auschwitz</title>
      <link>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/hmd2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/hmd2025/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m writing this on Monday 3 February, having been awake for about 18 hours on little sleep, so this is unlikely to be my finest prose. However, I wanted to write down this stream of consciousness while my memories were still relatively fresh, rather than delay and let the imprints fade.
On Sunday 2 February 2025, I visited Auschwitz-Birkenau for the first time. Earlier in the week, we had marked the 80th anniversary of the liberation of the camp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuff That I Like</title>
      <link>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/readinglist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 20:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/readinglist/</guid>
      <description>I wanted a place to talk about stuff that I like. If we have similar interests, you might enjoy something here.
P.S. you can&amp;rsquo;t use any of this for guessing my log-ins.
Books It&amp;rsquo;s quite hard for me to really make a good list encompassing all genres. So far, I&amp;rsquo;ve listed books in my main nerd fiction genres.
I find myself profoundly affected by recency bias when trying to think about other specific books to mention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why</title>
      <link>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/whyiwrite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danwright.org.uk/posts/whyiwrite/</guid>
      <description>Why do I have this site? While is slightly odd for a nobody like me to have a website, I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s unusual to want some sort of canvas for self-expression.
Besides, this is a very cheap hobby. I use a free GitHub account and a domain name costing all of £5.
Regarding the blog specifically, see Orwell&amp;rsquo;s reasons for writing:
Sheer egoism. It goes without saying. Aesthetic enthusiasm. I think a blog is a good outlet for creativity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
