<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dan Wright</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dan Wright</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bland Republicanism</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/republic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/republic/</guid>
      <description>Plenty has been written about the sorry state of British republicanism. Even as support for the monarchy declines, most people are, in my experience, quite sheepish about declaring republican beliefs.
This is not helped by the weakness of republican identity in this country. There are campaign groups &amp;ndash; of debatable efficacy &amp;ndash; but almost no symbols to rally around.
I admire the effort of the coronation protesters, and it is a disgrace that any of them were arrested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter of this Content</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/q4recs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/q4recs/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to make a very quick note of some of the better things I&amp;rsquo;ve read, seen, or listened to in the first few months of 2023 &amp;ndash; especially the new releases. I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to limit myself to one recommendation and one honourable mention in each case.
FilmPlease don&amp;rsquo;t judge me too harshly if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it, but Puss in Boots: The Last Wish is my favourite release of the year so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student Voice</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/clarevoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/clarevoice/</guid>
      <description>After I graduated in 2020, I was asked to provide an article for the Clare Review. I recently found a copy online while looking for something else. For posterity, I reproduce the following from said online version, which also features the excellent Jonty Townson and some nostalgic photos.Dan Wright (2017)UCS President
As the outgoing UCS president and a recent graduate, my final year at Clare was one of my best; for obvious reasons, it was also one of the worst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>219,948</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/covid/</guid>
      <description>I know that the following will probably come across as sentimental nonsense to anyone in their normal state of mind. This passing difference in perspective is a quite like that between dispassionately studying WW1 on the one hand, and attending an Armistice Day service on the other. Regardless, I think I&amp;rsquo;ll upload this and accept that I can cringe at my own sincerity.
Today was the second anniversary of the National COVID Memorial Wall, and I visited by chance during a break from the office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Write</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/why-i-write/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/why-i-write/</guid>
      <description>George Orwell is one of my favourite authors. His famous essay, which the title of this post references, is well worth a read.
To state the obvious: this is no great essay, and I am no Orwell. But I wanted to set out some of my reasons for having a blog. If you&amp;rsquo;re familiar with the motives for writing that he presents, you will recognise them in varying proportions in the below:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
